I was small. Pretty girls don't snore.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Good morning.
How is everyone doing? You all have been
texting me.
Um
every time I meet someone, they're
asking me about my YouTube channel and
I'm like, Oh my god.
And uh honestly, I love you guys. I love
how you guys have been checking on me,
but I'm doing great. I'm perfect. And um
I just stopped vlogging for a little
bit. Actually, I didn't even stop. It's
It's more of um So, the last video that
I posted Wasn't it the last video? The
Yeah, I think so. So, YouTube deleted my
video.
And uh let me tell you, when that
happened, I almost lost it. I was like,
uh-uh, ain't no way. Do you know the
hard work, the editing, the
I was so sad. I was so mad, but um it
was because um my video had had
copyright issues. But, normally when
your video has copyright issues, they
tell you, you know, you post and then
you post it private and then, you know,
you wait for all the you know, the
processing and stuff. So,
but when I waited, they said my video
was fine. And then after
uh after like after like 2 days actually
or 3 days, they said copyright. They
gave me a strike. They said my video was
immediately put down. I was like, ain't
no way. They didn't even give me a
choice to like remove the segment that
is that has copyright. No, nothing. They
just removed it and I was so sad because
the only option I had was to pay the
person I mean, the owner of the music
that I used. It wasn't even a music to
be honest. It wasn't even a song. It was
just like a small a small segment. I
don't even know how we ended up there,
you know, cuz it was not part of the
music that I wanted for my vlog. I
texted them. I was like, "Please, can
can you remove the strike?" And then
they're like, "No, that's not our that's
not part of our rules and regulations.
So, you have to pay the music that you
used." And I remember it was like 50
euros, 50 dollars, I remember. But I
remember I was so mad to the point where
I was like, "You know what?
Take it down. Take it down. I don't
care."
So, that's how that's what happened. I
was a little bit sad and cuz if you have
three strikes, apparently YouTube takes
down your channel. And my strike was
supposed
um it was supposed to end in July, which
we are in July already. So,
um hopefully there won't be any issue
like that. And voila, that's all that
happened. Maybe maybe in the future I'll
I'll try to repost it, you know.
Cuz I don't think a lot of people
watched it cuz it had 65 views 65k
views. Yeah. I was supposed to go to the
gym.
I ended up not going. Um so,
um I will have to work out at home. I'm
about to go and um
wait on Mohamed to come do my nails. I
have an appointment.
Anyways, I went to do my braids
yesterday. Let there be no meat. I'm so
sorry to get cute, but
I don't want I don't even want to tell
you who does my braids because the
minute I tell you guys, she's going to
be busy and booked. She won't have no
you know no space for me anymore. So,
I'm so sorry to get cute. If you know
her, good for you. If you don't, I'm so
sorry, but this is my woman cuz she does
the job.
Why did you say okay? I can send you the
location.
My nail guy is here. Ugh.
I didn't have no breakfast yet.
No stress. Okay.
>> [music and singing]
>> I saw that video. Oh my god. She was No,
that's not me. I don't snore like that.
>> Baby, yes you do.
>> No, I don't.
I don't snore. Pretty girls don't snore.
>> [music]
[singing and music]
>> I just finished doing my nails and I
love them so much.
Do you guys see this?
I don't know if you can see it.
I think these are the best nails I've
done so far.
I have a video shoot later on in the
evening.
>> [music]
>> I um I DJ random.
Romain is playing and uh so we're going
to go to the game.
And that's it for today.
I don't think I showed you guys my
braids.
But
these are the braids I got.
I swear I think I've been addicted to
knotless braids because
>> [music]
>> Do you know anything I do
that is different is I changed the
color. I had black.
And now I did a little bit of blonde
mixed with brown.
I'm hot.
I can't even show you guys my feet
because I think it's the same thing.
It's like a capri jumpsuit.
Does that make sense? A capri jumpsuit,
do you guys Do you get what I'm trying
to say?
And I don't like it.
What perfume should I wear tonight? What
should be the scent?
>> [sighs]
>> That's crazy.
That's sick.
What are they?
Voila. They had the whole day.
Like, what do you mean? First of all, I
got this perfume from Dubai, Yusuf Bar.
Um you guys can see them on TikTok.
So you go It's like a perfume factory.
This one Brenda mixed this one. I think
it was Baccarat Rouge with uh
with what? I don't remember, but I know
there is Baccarat Rouge with another
perfume. So it smells smells good.
Smells rich, you know?
>> [cheering]
>> Defense!
>> She's sweet.
She's sweet.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Woo!
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
>> [singing and music]
>> S Z
But it's a it's a really nice It's a
really nice place.
It's so so huge. It's so huge. It's so
big.
>> [laughter]
>> The The place is so lovely. The
environment is adorable, but the service
is great. I love that they they're
vegan, by the way. So, this is something
that is new. And no going asking for
chicken or beef. No.
Are you asking for chicken and all that?
But it was good. I love that, you know,
they have different perspective of food.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> But yeah, it was a nice Saturday. What
does it feel like it's Sunday?
I don't feel Sunday.
We are Saturday.
Saturday. No, we really had a good What
are we doing tomorrow, though?
Oh, me and me and we're going to to try
this acai bowls in um
in Kimi Hurda.
So, yeah.
Bye.
>> I never I never I never met somebody
that can look at they self as much as
you
>> Ah, baby, please. I don't even do that.
>> Not all the time, but after you get your
when you do your little
your little you know what I mean, your
self-care
after you get done with it
your nails, your hair, all that stuff,
your makeup, hey hey hey,
you don't leave that mirror.
>> Yes, I do.
>> No, you don't.
>> Yeah, I do.
Good morning, people. We are on Monday
and we're going to the gym.
What time is it?
8:30. I'm supposed to be there by 8:00,
but
>> No.
Are you sick?
I'm supposed to We were supposed to
leave the house by 8:15 for me to get to
practice on time. And you up here
talking about leave by 8:00. You didn't
even want to wake up this morning. We
going now.
We going now. Now.
No, now.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yeah.
It's beauty in the [music] struggle,
ugliness in the [singing] success. Hear
my words and listen to my signal of
distress. I grew up in the city and know
[music and singing] sometimes we had
less compared to some of my [\h__\h] down
the block, man, we were blessed. And
life [music] can't be no fairy tale, no
[singing] once upon a time, but I'll be
god damned if a [\h__\h] don't be trying.
[music] Sometimes
>> I don't know if I showed you guys my
my trainer, but this is a shimmy.
>> [music]
>> See her moving?
Do you see her?
So, I told her I want to be like her.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
[singing and music]
[music]
>> What up, beauties? I'm in I just came
back from the gym. I had a great
workout. It was hard, I'm not going to
lie,
but it was worth it.
So, I'm going to take a shower.
>> [music]
[bell]
[music]
[singing]
>> I just had a great [music] shower. Oh my
god, I feel so good.
>> It's Sunday at Cuban Mall.
You know this is our favorite spot.
We're waiting on our food.
We still like
This we should have been at Moving
Pictures swimming.
>> Huh?
Moving Pictures swimming?
>> out.
Feels Feels good outside being outside.
>> Moving Pictures good outside.
>> [music]
>> Make me a little smile.
Since when do you like matcha?
>> Who hates
>> Since when? The first time you you you
tasted it, you didn't like it.
>> I never did like matcha. Now you Now you
want to take credit for everything.
Okay, babe.
>> No, but I never I didn't introduce you
to matcha.
>> Okay, I thought I did.
>> I didn't say that. I'm just asking since
when cuz I never liked it.
And that's why you were on my side.
>> I tried it and it was good. You know
>> It tastes like grass.
>> I figured out I figured out a way they
can make it to make me like it, so
I ain't mad.
No, it's me.
>> Uh did I eat all I think I ordered some
pancakes.
Oh.
>> But if you don't If you don't
>> Food is Food is pricey.
>> Okay. And if you don't If you don't like
it
>> If I don't like what?
>> The pancakes. Yeah, yeah, you can have
the pancakes.
>> Okay.
>> I got pancakes though.
>> Mhm.
>> It's good, ain't it?
>> I always take some
in this seat.
>> Why?
>> Cuz I'll be too low for my food.
>> You want me to push your seat?
You want to push your seat closer?
This is what I ordered.
I wanted to try something new.
Bon appetit.
My serviette.
This better be good.
It's good.
>> It's good?
>> Mhm.
It has a lot of sugar though.
No, I'm not a sugar person.
Look at this bite.
>> Come here, please.
Try this now.
>> Let's see. I drop my husband home and
then I say, "Why not pop at XOXO bites?"
Cuz goodbye.
Oh my god.
That's nice.
So guys, the food was so good to a point
where
Of course this is a takeaway.
I'm taking some
and feel free to scan the code the QR
code.
Thank you XOXO.
You make sure you wear your belt.
Look at the view.
Voila.
>> I'm sorry guys if I sound This is my
teacher, Vansa.
I am so happy.
>> [gasps]
>> I passed.
>> [cheering]
>> It's a long story. I have a lot of
things to tell you guys.
>> [music]
>> After